[Music]
In the name of God, Rahap, the problems of
group 0 are at my service. Please
tell me who is the first person?
Number 38 Mr. Homaei
Mr. Homaei, please come, hello sir, don't be tired,
hello, good time, don't be tired. I
saw the theme of my second session. I didn't bother sending the exercise.
Now there is no problem. What was the problem in sessions one and two that
you saw? No, thank God.
I only made one original that I
sent as my exercise. I don't know. One is correct.
If you can look at it now, I'll look at it for
a minute. Now I'm not looking.
You talked about this original here for the gold case. Well, these are some
kinks that are
important to us now. Mr. Homaei, these are the lowest lows. But there are a
few kinks here that we
need to know from our left whether they are important
or not. Why? Because, let's look now. We need to
see which of these is the last king
that overcame a decision and created this low.
Now if I have a
new snake, yes, a new snake, gold. Let me
bring the gold. Please. Well, I looked at the
20th and 25th dates. The
24th and 24th are Monday's wires. Under 20, 24th. Yes, yes, yes,
30.  20 24 Well
Oh, we're going back
here, it's 20 24
Sixth and then I think it should be for here,
right, this is the tick
[Music]
Yes, this is the range, here let me check again, yes, that's it, for
sure, yes, this is it, well, go, you guys, here's the
kink that you
got in this area, this is the blue box,
this is it, we drew this box
here as the origin, well, do you have a
fish, let me tell you something, I drew the origin
for the lag, well, it's important,
but well, we have a series in four areas, and
now in the third session that will be sent to you tonight, it's an
important session, the third session, the fourth session, there are many
important sessions that we're talking about,
but now the last levy we have is here,
this is the bottom, so this levy came, what did it take?
First, we need to know that after the first
reversal, the first area that the price overcomes,
the opposite is formed,
we need to recognize it.  So, based on this, we will
consider a left turn
in the next session. These golfs that have two
sides, two highs, and lows that have two sides, I will
use this term for high and low,
not for king. This is one of those lows. When
the price has reached the area, it suddenly goes
below here, then goes up again. In the
next session, we will talk about this golf and these.
Here it becomes clear why this left turn is
important. The price has hit the lowest low and the first
area that should break upwards is
the kink that was formed at this price, that is,
here. So this should open an upward leg.
When this kink comes, it makes a decision to
go up. In addition to
facing this low and low and as a lap shoulder, it makes a
decision to start moving
upwards, that is, if it wants to overcome and break the upward leg. We will get to
these in the next steps.
But in order to understand now why
this kink is considered the origin of the movement or the
area that, for example, an order  It's
important for us to know that when this level is here, this golf,
we have a kink above it, which is a
decision to break this low, and when the
price wants to go up, this decision must
be overcome.  Here, the king is being priced out, as the
king returns and breaks again and
rides into this area.  When the price
breaks through these levels, it should return to this level and
be consumed.  But since it didn't come back
and used the same method again for the top,
meaning the price broke through the barrier of the bullseye on the way
here,
opened the path down, then went back and
engulfed the inner area of ​​the top here,
meaning the term engulfing engulfing here is
applicable to both of these levels.
When the price reopened the top with this here,
after it went to the target level, it
came to this left shoulder
and here it was
ordered. So now if this is an order, then in the
path it came to,
what is the kink?  The kink that resulted from
swapping this DP, which here if we
draw DP to DP, becomes this area, well, it
broke here, where did it break? When the price
hit the lowest two, it turned back, this pink pink low and
blue low. So here,
in the return, the first area that the price sees on its
way, this
becomes here. These are the orders that
are used in the step and this is the larger one,
meaning the origin of our movement. In essence, this
kink is why, because it came to this area, it was
formed. This was a decision that broke this low. What
was this low? Swap was an inking.
So now the origin for you in this area is the
lower box of this range from
here to this. This is the origin of the movement. So now,
why did the price fall here? Let's not
forget that here is the price when it came.
Let me change this. The price when it came
broke this low. It gave a series of signals before.
We will talk about these later
and what role does this play? This again
has the role of the left shoulder. What is the left shoulder? Left
shoulder, this low,
this king as a king.  LS is known, it is
now you say how can this be
left, why can't this one be right? Well, we learn
that some of these lines
that go up from the bottom make a point and then are hit under it.
Here, on the right side, as
an area, you call it symmetry, you call it QM, you call it Dakhram, I do
n't know, you call it shoulder, you call it everything. Let's
just learn that some of these lines are because there is
liquidity under them that the market
collects.  When you hit this low
above the price, that is,
when this low hits the top, you should take the view that it is the
bottom of this liquidity pool, and then
the price hits below this liquidity and then goes back
up. So because when it
hits below this liquidity, it will come back up again
in the future after it goes up and after it exits this hype, so to
speak, to consume this.
A
basic issue that
exists in RTM is that when the price
comes up, you become a buyer, it goes up again, it comes
under that buyer, that is, the
liquidity here takes below this and goes up
one higher, it waits for it to reload again, it
comes back to the same level. Now at this level, when it comes
here, it becomes a symmetrical QM head and it
depends on how long and how long you
take this return. Now you
are inking, so this box becomes the origin. Now
I will correct it and send it to you in your journal. I will
look at the rest of your journal tonight. I will
check this is the correction and this is the origin of the movement.
Well, the
rest.  I look at my journal, the rest of the exercises, one by one,
now after class, all the
journals, this is what I have,
this is what is broken before and then inside the broken face,
just take the trouble, Mr. Homaie,
write an explanation under each chart, did you mean which king did you mean? Was the
king broken before and then broken,
or aha, I mean the title, for example, one, yes, yes,
for example, a pair before and then now, if it was inside the four, it would
n't be a problem because some of my children sent them
in the order I sent them, from one to eight.
I tried to send them like that, yes, yes,
if it was possible, they would take the trouble to get
it, so the next news, number 37,
Mr. Mirzimi, don't be tired, hello, Mr.
Mirzimi, good
time for you too, let me bring your journal to you, what
number is your hand, yes, number
37, Mr. Reza, please, Mr. Reza,
I asked a question now, the admins took the trouble to
answer it, now broadcast it, Mr. Amir, do
n't hurt my hand,
they said that we should prioritize which
origin is more important now  I know
this prioritization is not a fixed thing.  Just
like, for example, your style is changing,
in those four periods of market leadership, it is doing something
for itself. Now, such
things are becoming more and more optimized. That's
right. Well, basically, that market is doing the same thing. It is
trying to stop and
prevent these things. Then, in the current state of
the market, based on your experience,
what is the priority?  For example, the picture that I wrote the question under is
a little higher in my journal.
I found two originals in it. One of them is the
result of a failure, that
is, a swap DP.
Yes, this red box is the swap DP. This is the
last one that was hit. This is the same orange box
that Mr. Nagi himself is planning to draw an LS.
One of the lows is before this. Now, which one is the
priority? How do we determine this priority? The
priority for us is to
be aligned. Now, you see, in gold, the origin is right there,
but it is not the reason why we should
order there. We have to
find the order based on where it hits. For the
core, that is, sometimes
when the price comes, this low creates
a series of structures before it comes. It works. It gives
reversal structures. Why do you see? There is a philosophy.
Before hitting the area, the market must
smooth its path back, that is, it corrects it. It is
impossible for the market, for example, suppose this way,
if this is not smoothed, it will
come with the area that we expect.
For example, like here, we expect here.  Let's buy
here. The market is
not making its way back. The price is going
up. We think it's going up. It's going to hit
this golf. But then it's going to hit this
area again. Then it's going up. It's going to
hunt our stops down there.
You're the origin, which is Mr. Naqim
himself. Tell me what date this is for.
Look at what's on the chart. I'm
saying, now I have to ask him. Let's see this
left four.
Now for this Levi. What we see here is
this low. This low is for breaking it. And this
low is for breaking it. This king.
And the swap that you drew here as the
start of the move
means the origin of the start of the move. Because after all, there has to
be an area that contains
orders to hit the left and start the path
up. Now, this box of yours for
swapping is my blue box. It's right. And the origin of the
move means the start of the move. After this
golf occurs, it can retrace to this area
and return. But this area that
Mr. Naqra drew, we have to see if there's
anything left.  For example, if there is an area
to the left of this low, for example, here on the chart, for example, if there is an area
like this, a king that
the price has broken, went up here, then
came back down and hit this again. When it hits this, this
king falls exactly opposite here
and it could be this origin of the move. I have to
ask Mr. Nqallam himself and
look at my chart, but you draw it based on the first
counter-decision opposite this origin. I will draw the
schematic here. See, suppose
we
have a low here, the price goes up, there is a
decision
that breaks this low.
In the first, that is, the price comes up from here, the
first
opposite, this kink broke this low and
now it has caused the low to break.
Sometimes the price will give this a reversal
like this,
then it will go and make this swap, and this
swap itself can have a distance from this
.  If it has a
large structure, it will come back to this top and
reach the lower area, but if not, this return
to this is what is important. We do
n't care about the bottom at all. This is the head and the bottom of the
head. This is important to us. This is one situation. The
second situation is that the origin wants to be correct.
When the price comes up from this low,
let it go up. Now, let's change this. When the price
comes up from this low, it makes one here
that makes both sides the same. That is, it comes as a
tacking. It covers this
when the top is empty. This does
n't need to go up like this and become more voluminous and it will figure it out on
its own. That is, if it
falls below it, we put a series of signs on it.
And there was another model in which,
for example, none of these two were there.
You see, it would have broken as a tacking. It would have gone
up. We consider this as the origin of the move.
Now, if on the chart, for example, we
come
here, if we have two lows next to each other,
that is, for example, here
and  This is the bottom of the list.
If we have a list here and a list next to it, let me give you
a minute.
This
[music] is the
lowest list here, and the list is the list of the list, and the list of the list has
started to rise from here. So, we are
looking at this list that we have here. We are looking at
what created this list. Look exactly. We are looking at what created this list.
Now this list is this king.
Is this king the result of something?  Yes, it is the result of
this origin. This origin is important. Yes, why is it important?
Because if you go a little further left to the left,
open
this low. Well, this is right. Maybe there is
no kink in this timeframe. But maybe in the
lower timeframe there is an area
that created this low and it was able to
hit the high and retrace itself. So,
this origin that exists here is the result of a
kink that did not react to it.
When the price hits the low, it returns and creates a low.
On the way back from this low, which is the
lowest high, you want to draw an origin.
Here, it is very easy. You come and say,
well, this area has hit the price bottom and the result of
that low is the left low. Now, on the right side, this can be used
as the origin. I have a reason for saying,
well, it has overcome the area opposite the
low. The low position is important. Look, this is right. The
low position. Yes, it is no longer needed. When
the price came, it hit the edge of this blue color. It has
done this amount of trace.
There is no order below this, so let's say it
becomes more voluminous.  So this could be the origin of the
upward movement. Did you notice that Miri Azimi is going to be great?  Yes, I understand, I
mean we have to look for a reason
to say that this left four is stronger than that
one.
Now, it should be settled.
What is the origin? For example, origin makes a move and you
ask for it later. If the market gives an inflow, here is
only one example. In some cases, this is the
best place for the origin to give a retracement.
Thank you very much.
Please let me look at your journal.
Of course, the ones you sent below, I
talked about your journal before,
but you didn't make many corrections. I looked at it myself,
and the admin
and the admin also did
some of the ones above that we
talked about. Now, there were some points that
we added. The line of the A is here. Admin, I'll
write it here for you. Okay, yes, I
tried to add time and
these. I put the symbol in the journal. Don't worry.
This is this time. I wrote it now. Some
friends will go and look. They cut it out so
that the FPI itself can go and investigate. They can't
find it. I don't have anything here anymore, not
this watermark.  It has a back that I don't know what
kind of territory it is, not here below, the
date is a little bit like this, they take it and send
it because sometimes you
do exercises, but in order to be able to see if
that origin is correct or not, we need
another area, a little bit more to the left.
Now, like here, we need to
bring it a little bit more to the left and take these out with reason.
Now, if it was already at the top
or bottom,
for example, there, we will examine a number of other signs, a number of other
reasons, a number of
other possibilities. Don't hurt your hand either. Thank you very much. The
next person will call this number 35,
Mr. Pouya.
Mr. Pouya, number 35. Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Yes,
don't be tired, Mr. Reza. I had two or three questions
about the
width. For example, we are using this left
shoulder only to see the left side of the market, is
that correct?   The
application
for
trading is
not here that we are finding now, so that we
can see the left side of the market, then
find the discussion of the dip or, for
example, see the shab, for me,
this discussion was raised in the previous position, for
example, something, for example, in a discussion between
the discussions, for example, this
width that broke before, then broke, then lap shoulder is
raised, so that we can look to the left, for example, have a
chart, for example, to see that, for
example, this, no, see that it broke before,
then broke, because if the king does
not break in its position and falls below it, we will not
come here and say that
now we have a break, look at my black,
we have an SNR here, so
when the price crosses this, it
understands that the price crosses this and makes a break on this
area, the king, well, this is another
kink, now the broken area and in the
right side, if it falls below it, we will come and examine the reasons,
why it fell below this, did it fall below it, is it a
breach and the price wants to fall lower,
and these, but the one that broke before  And then you
broke it and checked, is this more important than yourself?
Well, the king that broke before can
have a decision-making position for the break, and
what about the kings that broke later?  It can also
create a fake area for us if it has not formed on the breakout. For example, you think that this SNR line is
here and the price has not crossed this and
returned, it has formed above this. So if
it comes back to this in the future,
what do you expect? Is it because it
hit this golf under this kingo,
so it cannot give us that breakout and that inglepo or
that saw.   We
learn this because of this.  The market
uses this tactic a lot.  It comes on the
surfaces, breaks above the surfaces,
creates a shaky area, a fake kink.  It
creates a demand.  It makes this a very prestigious level
.  Then comes when all the selling here
hits below this and that means it falls in that
area right and then it comes back and
creates liquidity. This is for this situation,
that is, for just the fake-out situation, for example, we
use this, that is, we say we
know the fake, that for example, the fake is coming, yes, the king is
far from that area, that is
why now I will say something, I
said this the other day, just so that it is on the top of the
breakout area, not when we have a left shoulder, that is, a left, a low, a high, a low, a
high,
if we want to draw from this line and this kink
that you put here, one more time, so that I can come back and
draw this correctly, for example, this price line is going up from
here to
create a QM structure for us. In this area
that I am drawing a circle, we have a king here
called the king left shoulder kink. Now if the price
goes above this ceiling and hits back, that
will be the same QM, but if not, the price will change from this
decision that  This low has broken, meaning that
it falls within this range. Look, I'll draw it in blue.
It turns out that this low will break.
It comes back as a left shoulder LS. It will take
the price down, but if it goes up, it will be
QM. This is your exercise. Why did you
draw it the other way around?  No, I fixed it, I fixed it,
look at the bottom, I corrected it,
I sent it in a hurry, then I saw that it was not for something, I put it
down, I think it was right, let me
bring one of them, you want to correct it, I put it down, you
say schematic,
yes, you say schematic, schematic or something,
you say practice schematic, the top line, the bottom line, I sent it down, I said I put these wrong, you sent them down, apparently I made a mistake, I put them down again, oh, it's fixed, okay, delete those two lines, you're sending these instead, what we did
n't correct, but send it instead,
delete those two lines, don't let those two lines
stay in your journal, you're deleting them, oh,
right, I'm a student, I was
surprised at all that you sent this,
I'm later, I didn't draw it for a mistake, then I
fixed it, I sent it down, the rest, now I'll say a little bit,
I was a bit in my head, I
couldn't practice much this week, my class was a bit for
me, but I was able to get through it somehow,
but a lot  Mr. Boya, look at
this article
[Music]
[Applause]
Where were we, Mr. Boya? Where did you hear that the
lesson theme will be more difficult from the next meeting? Please,
you and other friends, take your time. All friends
are required to see all the troubleshooting, whether it
concerns your own group or the group of other
loved ones. In troubleshooting, we will
give you some tips
that may come in handy, and you can write these tips
in your journal as a
report.
Now, if necessary, we will give a good perspective
on it in the future. Well, there is another question, Mr.
Boya. Another question was that now I will
not take anything during class. For example, that candle
that comes, for example, breaks sharp, we consider that candle
as sharp, we
consider it as king, is that right? Or, for example,
we go to a lower time frame and optimize it. Is that
right? If you see, sometimes, for
example, this page that I have, now
I will delete this, we will draw this,
now we are here.  Suppose you have a Levi's that
broke,
this King broke,
then on the way back
when the price went up, here is a
broken curve. What does a curve mean? It means that
here you have a kink like this that
broke. Now it could be a King, it
could be a set of 10 to 10 Kings, but it
means that it doesn't have a structure, it
broke like this and the price went up.
Now you want to draw a box for this in
another case.
The trick is that you have a
range where this King, this King, this King broke the
core of this head. When will your range be? Well, to
optimize my entry, you can use this left one. That is,
here is the size of the spread
above this one. This is a trick. It is not 100.
Because at some point this single candle is long, it will
come again. For example, I use this.
But at the bottom of the range, it is always below the Levi's that this
single candle is broken. We have to
take all of this.
Then when the price doesn't have time here,
what does that structure mean?  That is, it
creates a reversal candle in it, then the price goes here,
for example, higher, a higher amount or two in the
future, and falls into this area, which can
be suitable for entry.  These should be, for
example, mostly on the FA side.
Well, here it can have a reaction and
this reaction can
lead to hitting a high. But
whether it can give a minimum price to Symmetry or the same QM
Loli or the same Left Shoulder
depends on everything. It depends on
whether the price comes from the high, where this low is
formed, and
everything else. Thank you,
Mr. Reza. Thank you, thank you. Please,
next person number 34, Mr. Mani. Hello, Mr.
Reza, good night. Hello, Mr. Mani. Good night, you too.
Live. Let me bring your journal.
Ask your question. Mr. Reza, thank you.
This is the last photo of my journal. Will you check it? Yes,
what do I do now? The last one
you sent? Yes, this is a red king
inside a big king. I had a question about this. The
last one that brought the price to the high.
Which one should we calculate? Which photo should I bring now? Those who have the
first photo, the one with the
initial schematic, I had a question. I had a question about that.
Ask them, which king, the price?
We
have to count the red king, which is in the heart of the big king, or we have to
count the big king. I'm
going to do twenty here now.
That's right. Yes, yes. Well, this kink that
you have here. Now look, change its color.
This kink that you drew here is red. It breaks the color of this
Minorio roof. For
example, this red kink comes and breaks this roof
.  The decision is for this ceiling and
when it returns from this high, it is
basically ignored here and
when it breaks this low, the price should
return to this
red range.  This means that reverse transactions are
created here, but if you increase your time from 15
minutes to 1 hour, your brain may
not see this.  Don't see this red.   At
that time, the last king will be the blue range for you. The
last king in the blue range means the king that has
recorded this high is always blue. But if you want to
optimize it, you will reach this red one. And in fact,
this red one is important for us to enter for selling. You should increase your
time, increase your pun, make it
an hour, daily, this blue one is the characteristic, and this
king that they say is the last king that is high is this high,
not red, but because in the return of pink,
blue cannot hold it. Where?  With
this red color you drew, when the trend line is
broken, the market will return to this
red area. Why?  There is a term called
ignoring, meaning here it is ignored. This is a decision
of a DP.
When this DP breaks this high
and a higher high is recorded here, it
should be held and sent up again.
Now what happens if it does not send up?
When it is broken below this, one here
becomes a high low, another low low high means a high
above here becomes a low below this, it
makes a low. So it means the trend can
return here, so the price can make this decision
again and this is the first return to this
area. No, it has been ignored. The price reaches it again.
But whenever they tell you which kink is the last
kink, this blue one created the last kink.
Thank you, sir. Please let me tell you
this. I answered in Zoom.
Now
here in the next one, please bring me one of the
next pictures. Give me a confirmation. Why
yes, tell me which one so I can bring you which one, which one is the second one?
We will bring the second one. This is a kind of picture. Well, this is a
copy and paste here.
This is their service.
Well, this is not one of the grids that they did.
This is now.  Right?  Is this DP schematic correct?
Yes, then Mr. Reza, since we want to
come and identify, if we
change our time, our DP will change, that is, we change it to
5 minutes or 15 minutes. Our DP will change. The
last king that reached that level
will change its place here, which
does not change. Now, in this, now, the last kink that put this level in
between here, the last kink that
broke this level, this will be right like this.
Yes, yes, but this has no meaning for us right now. Yes, it does
not. This is it. Now, if
you change your time, what do I know? Do it now,
make it 15, one hour. This will be deleted, but
this will remain. This will remain. This piece will remain.
If you do it again, for example, 4 hours and daily,
this itself may be deleted too, but this
blue RAM will be deleted. There must
be a larger structure here, for example. Mr. Reza, that's
right. We need to identify from the red one on the left.
Let's find the front of the DP. That's
right, because this red one created the blue one.
And here the area
you drew in white has
overtaken the blue area and created a low
and the team's decision
to create a low is
true. Then, Mr. Reza, if the DP in this golf becomes
a sign, it's back, it's back. Yes, for example,
if this can hit here like this,
turn around, hit a low down, and hit it on the back again, and
throw this hit. We have, we have
thousands. This is a sign that you should
go find a target at that time. What is the target for
?  For this area, you need to find the target here,
hit it, this one comes behind this and
goes behind higher. Thank you, Ares, please, I'm here to
answer.
I sent it to Taqrin. If you give me a payment, I'll
look at it. Mr. Amani, I'll
look at everything. I'll look at everything with my free
time. I'll answer everything tonight.
Thank you for your kindness. Please, please  There is
a situation that is formed.
Mr. Baghi, I see a situation on the chart.
It is like this: the price comes here,
for example, it forms a king
before it breaks this. So, before it
breaks this, how exactly does this happen
?  I mean, if I were to go into more detail, it would be like this:
We
have a king that when it comes down, it creates an
origin, then it goes down,
now when it comes back up, this kink
comes before it breaks the top. Basically, it goes like this.
Yes, yes, yes, this happens a lot. It happens a lot in chat. It
goes into this hole here.
Can this DP be a solid place or
not?  No, no, no, they shouldn't hit their backs.
Then, yes, here, sometimes, this one comes
from the top or opens up somewhere.
It can break under this. But after
breaking this verse, it can come immediately. It can hold it. That
is, it has to come from this and not hit anything from the left. It can decide
here. Oh, let's
come immediately. It can decide.
Yes, I saw
this Lo, this Lo, who is looking here,
here, he breaks a king, a king here,
and touches it and hits these. He sits down and holds it. He
goes up.
This is an example, but if it gets too long, for
example, he has the range here to in-golf. He
can come under this. For example, he comes under
this Lo, he in-golfs here. Because then, he can
maybe want this left down because
this one hasn't hit the target area. Come
here, take it.
That presence of that origin is important. What if it's not there
?  Because you know, if this is not the case, we should go and
check this low first. Yes, if this
low was strong, its presence would
not have been important. When the price falls, you
should go below this low. No, you
should not consider these ranges
because this is not strong. It has a breach in itself. It is
bigger and the only area that
can stop it is this. And now, if you
don't stop it, you should go below this
low and look for it. Think about it a little bigger.
Then the next question is this, Mr. Reza, that we are in the live
market and we want to trade DP.
Sometimes, for example, suppose there are several SNRs.
Do we also look at the time frames?
For example, we look at how much our leg is now.
Which one do we expect? We will
talk about this later. That's right.
We always come up from the time. We
always look at the daily, weekly, monthly time.
And from the daily time, that is, at the beginning of the week, for example, a
chart like this opens.  Let's
open this chart here and look at the beginning of the
week.
What is the position of this trend at the beginning of the week?
What direction is the price going? We'll examine all of this.
Then, in relation to them, we'll look at the time
below. The big time trend gives the direction. That is, it
moves in that direction throughout the week. We know,
based on the direction that the big time trend gives, that
this week it's going to go up
next week. When it hits this back and
hits this low, we say it's a downtrend. We'll move accordingly.
If there's no high time trend, it's
impossible to work with the low time trend because it's too fractal.
Putting these together becomes difficult. Yes, my
last question is, we're talking about kings that
form, for example, a high or a low. I do
n't mean DPA, for example, the ones you say that the
last king that pulled the high, do
you consider those kings important to hold or not?  Can't
hold 'em.  Hold cannot have no hold at the moment
.  Okay, it can't be.   It
may not be.  Now, for example, if we
see another good example here, suppose it's a
kinky guy who freaked out and leaked.
Yes, this king global has doubled and the
price comes here.
This cake makes this
ingolf or f because its pair goes like everyone else. It hits the back of
an area and then drops. Yes,
the kink that did this is this. It's
true here. You didn't do a holi either.
Yes, yes, so being a hold. Holding on the
last king can be a big deal, but
in capsa capsa capsa, this towel is important.
For example, this rally base drop, this
trick becomes important
or this trick. Now in this case, I say
that this is more important. A. Here is more important.
Yes, I have this. I have a model. One is that the
price goes here, holds here, then breaks down, comes
down, which is the same as the kicker. And
this. Yes, it doesn't have a chance. Yes, but if after holding
this area,
this area that breaks, it
comes back inside, that is, after this golf has retraced
and this jump is not a big deal for us in the future.
Now, I said caps myself.  This is the cap,
something I'm referring to now. In the tutorial, I
say a def cap, but it's a very important topic.
For example, everyone here probably knows it,
but I'll say this cap again. I'll
talk about it in the meeting. Thank you very much. Please don't
hurt your hand.
Thank you. Please. Score
31. Mr. Monshizadeh.
Hello, Mr. Reza. 1. Hello, sir.
How are you?  Okay, don't worry,
I have a question that I had in my journal.
Look at it. I understood correctly. And I have a
question that I had. Is the original the same as the
Els King?  It could be, it could be, it could
be. Then we usually
trade it more with Alsou or Origina,
right?
We have a whole philosophy of trading.
Of course, trading is done with two hands.
Trading on the door, for example, in turns, after the
price turns up, if you consider the direction of the Chinese market, it can have a
range that can be reversed
after a reversal opens from above.
We trade this way.  First we'll learn what the
pass is, then look at these two
things.  One is a fake, the other is original.
We can trade these two things when we get back
.  Our general trading philosophy is based on the same
principle that the lift I mentioned goes up and hits one of the
decision areas.  This is not because, for
example, you can trade in another way.   The
market is a
decision-making type. This can be traded at the moment.
For example, if we have a region that has
been held, we have a king. It breaks this,
meaning it breaks the bottom. We do
n't expect this kink to return. We expect
the price to go down. But it
doesn't work when it returns. What does it do? The price
comes. Yes, it breaks. It breaks
here. It makes a kink.
Well, if, for example, it has dominance
and a person knows, for example, in the live moment, it is very important to
know that this, for
example, is not bulky. This low has gone to a
left. This is not bulky here in the market. It means that in the
formation of a kink, you can trade and sell. It is very
difficult, but you can hold it. When it
hits behind these, it
goes back to this FTB. It
trades this for a new ceiling. This is another type of trade.
These can be done together. This can be done in a structure with the
market. It can be done behind this. It can be done by
deciding to trade. I traded on the left, which is the same situation.  It's
Engelfingelf
who
said that the two highs are two highs in color.
I'll explain about it in session 4. One question. We
get the origin in the components of the king. Right.
The components. Yes, yes. That is, in the S king,
we can get the origin again. For example, a
king. A king. This king. If it's on the ares.
If it's under the ares. And if it's on the left. The king itself is in the
structure at a lower time.
Suppose this king is a delay. When you time it for
an hour, you can get all the components for it. You know,
and we have a king. One minute of this
one minute is not needed. For example, its range is
7 pips. You don't need to go over there and get the
details because it won't work anymore. You have to
go in 5 seconds. Now, the whole bottom bit. If you
want to trade, it's a two or three pip difference. That's it.
If there's a data discrepancy or something like that, it's
lost. It won't go down anymore.
Usually, the time doesn't go down anymore unless the other
party wants to put a very small stop loss.
Just a question for practice.  I'm mostly
practicing on 5 minutes, it's okay because we've been
used to 5 minutes for a long time, I mean I
can't go
higher than that.
For example, this 5 minutes is okay because the 5
minute entry time is one minute, but if
you can shift it a little higher, 15 minutes
later, you can send me a more accurate chart. For example, right now I
have a problem with your chart. For example, I'll bring this here and
tell you. Now I'll review these exercises at
night, but this is one thing. I'll
delete this here and here.
Look at the pace. For example, if you sent this chart in this state,
double-click here. Here, this is the frame, up and
down. You want it to fall. This is for gold. This is the
top of it. This is the bottom of it. For example, you
zoomed in a little bit. It's hard to understand. For example, no
one can understand the story of this piece
.  Now the good thing is that it has history and all that
.  For example, this time people come and watch,
but it would be better if it was a bit like our previous practice
.
Before I
send you a small, small one, aha.  I wanted to see if I had
drawn my Retrisa line accurately, and everything would be clear at the end
.  See what I'm saying?  At the end of this
kick with this low, it's clear
here without referring to the chart. Now,
for example, you can write this here, Sking,
yes, where is Elsking?
Look at this. Of course, this is
where the higher high is, which is an S-arm. I threw it.
Now, the ratio of the previous DP is that yes, yes, yes, I
got it compared to this. I wanted to see if I got it right. I
mean, I had a question about the Left Shoulder
King method. You and the other friends
here can do it. Here, it's right. Hi, Low, Low, we
got this. What does El Spin
mean? I think that's the one I
got from DP. DP. It's Elskin. Right.
No, this is now compared to here. If Low is
Low, you have to specify these. Then
write here. SK Left Shoulder Kane.
Now, this is as when it goes below this. Who else can we
say?
Lol, but now it's ignored and the price
is sitting on this verse. Now, why
did you get this? Aha, this. DP.
But well, this should have been taken. This should have been
corrected. This is completely separate training.
I didn't come to fix it. A DP broke before. I
just got it. The sharp broke. The screw is like this.
Yes, this is red.
Why is it red? The kink is exactly like this. Then
this would be the two DPs that you see on the
LS. Because I was confused. I did
n't know how to figure it out on the chart.
DP3 is like the one that doesn't show up now. This is
now DP3 or D. How can it be?
I didn't understand myself. This is the kink that you
figured out here.
Well, since the price came out, there have been
expectations of buy here. Here are expectations of sell.
Sorry. In this area of ​​the screen, there have
been expectations of sell and it has been ignored. This is the
ignoring. When it goes behind these
cliffs and on the first turn, yes, that
double position. This doesn't go straight to the left anymore. That means the
straight position of the left shoulder doesn't go straight. I just
drew a few for my friends. On the left
for my night, let's talk about it again in their journals in troubleshooting. It does
n't go there anymore. It should have been with a left. Now let me see. Find
one here.  I
don't want to come there anymore. Let's get
this left shoulder for him. He's coming.
A low and a left low. Well, you're
considering it as a king. Now, in this state,
let me see.
Well,
the lows
[music]
Now, look here
at this area.
We want to make a
decision for this board.
Well,
you're in that, for example, it's bearish. Now, we
want to make a decision for this low.
Well, what did this low
create?
Why did it break a low and create a low?
That's what we have now. Now, let's go down time by time.
For example, here it's kinking,
but let's assume there's no left. And that's it. Well,
the kink that takes this shape
becomes a box here.
This swap is red. So, when the price creates this low,
on the first turn, meaning the price
wants to come up, it should
break or break this area of ​​the blue box. We
expect it here because there's no break. We'll
use this single candlestick. There's no break anymore.
Then this blue box here.  A single candlestick is the
limit of the decision to break this low
that the price hits on the first reversal, it reacts,
that is, it hits it here, it
reacts, then this is the
right decision method, right, so this was the result of the failure of this
kink, this is no longer in line with the left,
but well, it was the result of the failure of this left, this
left and on this swap that created this low,
this is the
last one, I don't understand what happened to that
multiplication, well, look from the left, come to the right from the left
here, I'm writing, look again,
what created this low, this low that broke here, didn't it
break? Yes, yes, well, when it breaks this
low, it also created this low. Now,
when the price goes back up, its first obstacle is this.
Now, if the method overcomes, it becomes a decision that
overcomes the decision, so it holds this price
because the decision
went to this area. Now, if it comes from above again, it
wants to break, this area must be broken.
When this doubt breaks, anything that breaks this means anything
that breaks this low, this low becomes a low. Yes, it
becomes the decision of this one low
that came again.  The one that broke is the one that broke. Yes, you
did. This way, there's no need for a lift.
And these, these, I say, we'll put these in
the place where our aloes are colored. Now, the next two sessions, we'll get to it.
Now,
in the next session, we'll look at it. Now, look at
my journal. If there's a problem anywhere, tell me so I can see if I
understand the concepts of the sessions correctly. Because I said, I
mixed up the breaks with the style we
worked on. That's because it's different now. So,
for one, I'm
afraid that when the breaks are broken, when the breaks are broken. I'm
drawing them the other way around. I want to see if they're
correct. The exercises I did were taught. I practiced them,
but I didn't send them
because I said the D session was already taught. I was practicing the
first one. I was drawing them wrong in the retries.
Then, I said, in the
D session, when I practiced, I sent them to see if I understood the lines, the
retries, and the breaks. I
understood them correctly. I understood the DPs correctly.
Yes, okay, I'll
check them. Keep an eye on me.  I'll
check this.
Thank you very much.  Thanks, yes, that's it,
remember that
from the answer.  Okay.  In the name of God, I greet you and have a good
time, my dear companions and friends
.  We are very happy to be with you with the new
Zeus Group Trading Course
.  This course is published in its entirety in a
dedicated playlist of the same name on
Zeus' official YouTube page at Zeus Forex Channel,
and all sessions can be viewed in order from the
first episode.  In this course,
you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After
watching each session, you can practice
and then watch 6 short half-hour sessions of
troubleshooting by friends who participated in the round
to get a better understanding of the material.
After that, enter the next teaching session.
To communicate directly with us and use the
troubleshooting plans, simply send a message to the Telegram ID of
Zeus Group Underline of this admin and
stay in touch with us.  Wishing you all success
in your trading career, my
dears.
[Music]